Finding Aid for Law Library (University of Michigan) Publications, 1967-1989
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Law Library (University of Michigan) publications 1967-1989
University of Michigan. Law Library.
.5 linear feet
9735 Bimu C430 2
Includes annual reports, brochures and pamphlets, manuals such as A Guide to Legal Research, programs, regulations for library use, and reports.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Publications are received periodically from the unit.
The Law Library publications are open to research without restriction.
For a historical note on the Law Library see the finding aid for law Library (University of Michigan) Records.
The Law Library Publications Include annual reports, brochures and pamphlets, manuals such as A Guide to Legal Research, programs, regulations for library use, and reports.
Subjects:
University of Michigan. Law Library.
Genre Terms:
Annual reports.; Pamphlets.; Manuals.; Programs.; Regulations.; Reports.
- Publications
  - Unit Publications
    - Annual Reports, 1984-85, 1985-86 (Box 1)
    - Articles
      - "Building a Foreign Law Collection at the University of Michigan Law Library, 1910-1960" (by Margaret Leary, 2002 (Box 1)
    - Brochures
      - Miscellaneous, 1967-1988 (Box 1)
    - Guides
      - Public Catalog Guide (1983) (Box 1)
      - Tape Tour #1 & #2 (1983) (Box 1)
      - User's Guide (1982) (Box 1)
    - Manuals
      - A Guide to Legal Research, 1976-1987, 4 volumes (Box 1)
      - Introduction to Legislative Materials and Legislative Histories (1982 1983) (Box 1)
    - Programs
      - Dedication: Law Library Addition, 1981 (Box 1)
      - The Legalization of American Society: A Symposium Commemorating the Dedication of the Law Library Addition, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Regulations
      - Selected Library Rules, 1967 (Box 1)
    - Reports
      - Automation for the University of Michigan Law Library: Final Report (1989) (Box 1)
      - Introduction to Sources of International Law at the University of Michigan Law Library (1983) (Box 1)
      - Law School Building Program Report and Statement (Box 1)
      - List of Publications (1983) (Box 1)
      - University of Michigan Law School Capital Campaign and Guidelines (Box 1)